Guide to the Pierce County Central Labor Council Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Pierce County Central Labor Council records, 1942-1989; 1947-1986; 2882-004; 15 cubic feet (15 boxes)
  - Series IV: Related Corporate Bodies, Committees, and Projects, 1942-1986 (Box-folder 5/1-5/34; 7/19; 9/2-9/21; 10/1-10/11; 12/8-12/28; 13/1-13/11; 13/17; 14/6-14/23; 15/1-15/21)
    - Subseries C: Building Project: New Labor Center, 1963-1977 (Box-folder 12/13-12/28; 13/1-13/11)
      - Elevator Maintenance Contracts, Central Labor Council, 1973 (Box-folder 13/2)
      - Dunham-Bush, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 13/3)
      - Building Loan, State Mutual Savings Bank, 1970 (Box-folder 13/4)
      - Correspondence and Appraisals Regarding Long-Term Financing, Labor Center, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 13/5)
      - Proposed Liens Filed on New Labor Center, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 13/6)
      - Record of Payments-Washington Electric Company, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 13/7)
      - Record of Payments-Wise Plumbing, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 13/8)
      - Record of PaymentsChaffee Zumwalt, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 13/9)
      - Record of PaymentsLarson Signmakers, 1972 (Box-folder 13/10)
      - Record of PaymentsPacific Hardware & Specialties, 1972 (Box-folder 13/11)
    - Subseries D: Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1975-1984 (Box-folder 14/6-14/23)
      - Registration Drive, 1984 (Box-folder 14/6)
      - Pierce County Committee on Political Education, 1983 (Box-folder 14/7)
      - Statewide Candidates, 1982 (Box-folder 14/8)
      - Committee on Political Education (COPE) Newspaper Clippings and Letters to the Editor, 1982 (Box-folder 14/9)
      - Committee on Political Education (COPE) Candidate Screening Committee, 1982 (Box-folder 14/10)
      - Registration Drive, 1982 (Box-folder 14/11)
      - Endorsement Information, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 14/12)
      - CorrespondenceCommittee on Political Education (COPE), 1980-1981 (Box-folder 14/13)
      - Newspaper Clippings & AdvertisementsCommittee on Political Education (COPE), 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14/14)
      - Legislative IssuesCommittee on Political Education (COPE), 1981 (Box-folder 14/15)
      - Statewide Candidates, 1981 (Box-folder 14/16)
      - Education Committee (1 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box-folder 14/17)
      - Education Committee (2 of 2), 1975-1981 (Box-folder 14/18)
      - Tacoma Dome Celebration, 1983 (Box-folder 14/19)
      - Centennial Celebration, 1984 (Box-folder 14/20)
      - Labor Day Picnic, 1984 (Box-folder 14/21)
      - Downtown Tacoma Days, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 14/22)
      - Committee on Institutional Industries, 1983 (Box-folder 14/23)
    - Subseries E: Solidarity Day, 1975-1986 (Box-folder 15/1-15/21)
      - Tacoma Public Utility Rate, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 15/1)
      - EPA Asarco, 1983 (Box-folder 15/2)
      - Substance Abuse Seminar, 1986 (Box-folder 15/3)
      - Union Label Committee, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 15/4)
      - Economic Opportunity Committee (1 of 2), 1975-1983 (Box-folder 15/5)
      - Economic Opportunity Committee (2 of 2), 1975-1983 (Box-folder 15/6)
      - Solidarity Day VI (1 of 2), 1986 (Box-folder 15/7)
      - Solidarity Day VI (2 of 2), 1986 (Box-folder 15/8)
      - Solidarity Day V (1 of 2), 1985 (Box-folder 15/9)
      - Solidarity Day V (2 of 2), 1985 (Box-folder 15/10)
      - Solidarity Day IV, 1984 (Box-folder 15/11)
      - Solidarity Day III, 1983 (Box-folder 15/12)
      - Solidarity Day Expense, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 15/13)
      - Solidarity Day Expense, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 15/14)
      - Mailing Lists Requests for Supplies Solidarity, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 15/15)
      - Solidarity II Mailings and Forms, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 15/16)
      - Public Employee Committee (1 of 2), 1976-1986 (Box-folder 15/17)
      - Public Employee Committee (2 of 2), 1976-1986 (Box-folder 15/18)
      - Financial Reports Solidarity, 1981 (Box-folder 15/19)
      - Correspondence Solidarity, 1981 (Box-folder 15/20)
      - Flyers Letters of Invitation Promotion Solidarity, 1981 (Box-folder 15/21)
    - Subseries F: Other, 1971-1985 (Box-folder 7/19; 9/2-9/21; 10/1-10/11; 12/8-12/12)
      - Election Material, Initiative 412: Reducing Consumer Interest Rates, 1982 (Box-folder 7/19)
      - Jobs and Justice Rally (oragnized by Washington State Labor Council) Material, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 9/2)
      - Initiative 412 Fair Signature Campaign Material, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 9/3)
      - Initiative 412 Speakers Kit, 1982 (Box-folder 9/4)
      - Air Quality Citizens Advisory Committee Materials (1 of 2), 1978-1979 (Box-folder 9/5)
      - Air Quality Citizens Advisory Committee Materials (2 of 2), 1978 (Box-folder 9/6)
      - Tacoma-Pierce County Economic Development Board Materials, 1976-1983 (Box-folder 9/7)
      - Tacoma-Pierce County Economic Development Board Executive Committee Materials, 1979 (Box-folder 9/8)
      - Tacoma-Pierce County Economic Development Board Executive Committee Materials, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Tacoma-Pierce County Economic Development Board Executive Committee Materials, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 9/10)
      - Elder Care Association, 1977 (Box-folder 9/11)
      - Future of Work Participant's Folder and Related Articles, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 9/12)
      - Future of Work Conference Materials, 1973-1980 (Box-folder 9/13)
      - Employee Assistance Program, 1977 (Box-folder 9/14)
      - Tacoma/Pierce County Opportunities Industrialization Center, 1977 (Box-folder 9/15)
      - Private Sector Initiatives Board, National Guard Project, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 9/16)
      - Metropolitan Park (Tacoma) District Board, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 9/17)
      - Price Watch, AFL-CIO, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 9/18)
      - Private Sector Initiatives Executive Committee, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 9/19)
      - Prisons in Pierce County, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 9/20)
      - Stanford Research Institute (SRI), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 9/21)
      - State Labor Studies Advisory Committee (1 of 2), 1977-1979 (Box-folder 10/1)
      - State Labor Studies Advisory Committee (2 of 2), 1977-1979 (Box-folder 10/2)
      - Steilacoom Prisoners' Support House (Tacoma, WA), 1977 (Box-folder 10/3)
      - Tacoma Community College, Fort Steilacoom Community College, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 10/4)
      - Tacoma Community College Foundation, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 10/5)
      - Tacoma International Trade Day, 1982 (Box-folder 10/6)
      - United Fund Cutbacks by ALF-CIO/United Way, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 10/7)
      - United Way National Right to Work Campaign, 1982, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 10/8)
      - Wilderness Area Task Force/Cougar Lakes Proposal, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 10/9)
      - Work-Education Council, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 10/10)
      - Center on Work and Productivity, 1979 (Box-folder 10/11)
      - "A Quality Working Life" Seminar, Tacoma Club, November 13, 1978 (Box-folder 10/12)
      - In-Service Workshop for Teachers, 1983 (Box-folder 12/8)
      - A Day at the Union Hall, 1982 (Box-folder 12/9)
      - Pierce-Kitsap Labor Studies Advisory Committee, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 12/10)
      - Leases, Labor Temple Corporation (1 of 2), 1972-1977 (Box-folder 12/11)
      - Leases, Labor Temple Corporation (2 of 2), 1972-1977 (Box-folder 12/12)